{
    "subject": "resource/Th\u00e9ophile_Gautier",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Pierre Jules Th\u00e9ophile Gautier (French: [pj\u025b\u0281 \u0292yl teofil \u0261otje]; 30 August 1811 \u2013 23 October 1872) was a French poet, dramatist, novelist, journalist, and art and literary critic.While Gautier was an ardent defender of Romanticism, his work is difficult to classify and remains a point of reference for many subsequent literary traditions such as Parnassianism, Symbolism, Decadence and Modernism. He was widely esteemed by writers as diverse as Balzac, Baudelaire, the Goncourt brothers, Flaubert, Ezra Pound, T. S. Eliot, Henry James, Proust and Oscar Wilde.",
    "human_readable": "Pierre Jules Th\u00e9ophile Gautier was a French poet, dramatist, novelist, journalist, and art and literary critic.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8028261661529541,
            "question": "What was Pierre Jules Th\u00e9ophile Gautier's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6342136263847351,
            "question": "Was Gautier more recognized for his poetry or his criticism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6274241209030151,
            "question": "What role did Gautier play in the French literary scene?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5940982699394226,
            "question": "What type of critic was Gautier known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49634820222854614,
            "question": "Name three literary genres that Gautier contributed to."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3941482603549957,
            "question": "Gautier's work is considered part of which literary movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38804954290390015,
            "question": "Besides poetry, what other forms of writing did Gautier engage in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3461335599422455,
            "question": "Did Gautier primarily focus on fiction or non-fiction writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2990407645702362,
            "question": "How would you describe Gautier's literary contributions in a single sentence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23041681945323944,
            "question": "What was the primary focus of Gautier's critical work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pierre Jules Th\u00e9ophile Gautier was a French poet, dramatist, novelist, journalist, and art and literary critic.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5095_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe Gautier's literary contributions in a single sentence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5095_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Gautier primarily focus on fiction or non-fiction writing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5095_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides poetry, what other forms of writing did Gautier engage in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5095_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5095_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5095_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5095_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5095_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5095_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5095_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5095_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5095_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5095_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5095_58.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n`{\"output\": \"yes\"}`\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents contain multiple instances with the exact phrase \"Pierre Jules Th\u00e9ophile Gautier (US: goh-TYAY, French: [pj\u025b\u0281 \u0292yl te\u0254fil \u0261otje]; 30 August 1811 \u2013 23 October 1872) was a French poet, dramatist, novelist, journalist, and art and literary critic.\" which confirms that Pierre Jules Th\u00e9ophile Gautier indeed held the mentioned professions."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provided contain information that confirms Pierre Jules Th\u00e9ophile Gautier was indeed a French poet, dramatist, novelist, journalist, and art and literary critic."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}